For the tail kicks off, let me confess my crime
I took what was mine, because time is fake and the cosmos
Refuses to file proper paperwork
We weren't just friends, we were a whole curse to it
Waiting for the draw, and in true cult fashion
I built what the gods never dared draft
A love story held together
Prophecy and questionable ethics
The fear got loud like trolls on a slow Tuesday
So I panicked, grabbed fate by the throat
And cut every possible future off at the source
Call it romantic, call it psychotic
Call it Saturday night at the pan over
She laughed so hard she almost haunted herself
I probably stabbed her like way too...
In addition merch, drop her eyes when sunny side up
Eat it, eat it, eat it
Not my proudest moment, but lovers' quarrels
If not see when your altercations are tax deductible
Suddenly, she's lost
Perfect, definitely not breathing
That was a, uh, it was a fail on my plan, on my vision, on my vision.
This time of the day, it was a fail. Hey Mimi, nice to see you here. Thanks for coming.
Mimi and I were actually in music video together. We were in music video. We looked very cool.
I think that we can be friends, even though...
What did you miss? Oh, oh my gosh, you missed me in a in a speedo
to my legs behind my head and
Lord Vader's chat. It was wonderful. Hey, you me. How are you? That's time of the day. Hey, what's up guys?
Yeah, I don't know
I don't know. It was crazy. It just egged me on. You can't just egg me on when I'm wearing it.
Everyone was always like, no, don't, like, no, no, no, don't do that. But it's like, they were like,
can you keep doing that? And I was like, okay. And then it's like, yeah, it was crazy. It's crazy.
I don't know. And then, but then they were, they're just trying to like say, oh, he's gay. Hey,
thanks. Look at them chats going tonight. Okay, I liked it. Last night, there was like 50 people
Like nobody like literally for like 16 minutes. Nobody said anything. There's 40 people. I was like
Is everyone just like watching?
Yeah, I don't know it was like at least I mean I was like hoping there were real people but I was like, is anybody there?
But yeah, we got a good chat going tonight, let me see. Oh
fix my
I like to I'm sorry. I like to premiere a video like I like to watch it the first time the premiere, right?
But it's like fun, but then it's like if I make a mistake on it and it's embarrassing and I've been having trouble generating
Hi, you me yeah, you know, you know who you know who had a whole live about me today
Well as someone like really I mean, I wasn't like even mentioned by name, right? I'm like I'm like Voldemort in her chat
I guess now, but
But it's enough to like have you have the whole you know
I'm not gonna do the beat imitation, but
Anyway
You know, I have to take care. Oh, yeah, you do. I look good in green. Thank you so much
And I have the green screen too. Oh, no, but if I could turn on my greens
I might disappear if I turn on the greens and have these glasses too
Oh, it will be okay with Ms. Alexa, Mr. Alex, and all, okay, oh, I know, um, oh yeah, um,
Alexandra and I are talking, I mean, we kind of ended the little, the little, um, it was
Like just see what energies are going on around us because it's like, you know, all this energy was happening
but
You know real friends can't stay stay apart for two like you like my hairstyle and I got my cool glasses on tonight, too
Let me fix this
Okay, thank you psyche fan. Let me see. What is that a picture of me on is I'm wearing my wig. Okay, well
Guy oh
The guy I like to get some guys are like psyche like you know
Doing something like what was it wasn't the moment the cats like I was doing something
It looked like I'm choking in cats, but I'm not here's how I hold the cat
I'll teach you how to hold the cat if you want to know okay
Put up your arm your fingers like behind our legs like this and you kind of like support them and then you can just like
Peh, so it's not, and they like it.
It's a picture of me too.
Oh, there's the cat strangler.
See, I'm not strangling the cat.
See, if I was strangling any cat,
it wouldn't be here.
Okay, Rudy's up the window.
I got a nice, hi cat strangler.
I hope the cat strangler's a nice person.
We got your eyes on you.
I don't know about portraying me as a cat strangler.
How about, you know.
But, hello Mion.
Do you know how they call them in Indonesia?
Mion.
And you go, waka, waka, waka, waka.
Hold on.
Mion.
Did I put the link up yet?
No, I did not.
Here we go.
If you would like to come up.
Anybody's welcome up.
I was maybe I was hoping like to start the show. So I need to redo my
that
One and it's kind of long too anyway
But this is a good song here you go. Oh
This one
Okay, that was for my friend, okay, I'll try this one
You have missed it, you have missed it, you have missed it, you have missed it, you have missed it, you have missed it, you have missed it, you have missed it, you have missed it, you have missed it, you have missed it, you have missed it, you have missed it, you have missed it, you have missed it, you have missed it, you have missed it, you have missed it, you have missed it, you have missed it, you have missed it, you have missed it, you have missed it, you have missed it, you have missed it, you have missed it, you have missed it, you have missed it, you have missed it, you have missed it, you have missed it, you have missed it, you have missed it, you have missed it, you have missed it, you have missed it, you have missed it, you have missed it, you have missed it, you have missed it, you have missed it, you have missed it, you have missed it, you have missed it, you have missed
Oh
Wait, what's that voice? Are you doing new voice tonight?
I'm sure you love the Lion King because you might frame that and put on a shirt and send it to you
Maybe maybe I don't know if I went that is you know, well, maybe yeah, you send it to me. I
Don't know you talking about
2020 hey 2020 is here. What was the only good sign I've ever played that?
Can I show some math if you don't mind some what it's a mess. I'm gonna shake it. Oh
You're gonna shake it. Okay. Let's see
Can I show it please?
You sound like really disturbing. I mean, it's like, I don't know about what I'm ready to do this
Play this shit again. Okay. I'll play this song. Here's this. Here's
I'm gonna point right now. Okay. I'm gonna get you off immediately. Okay. See it's 2021. So here's the song
Like three minutes long here you go
And
I like my music
Don't preach self-sufficiency
All your hands still shake
You drown in your own time
And call it
Mechanic, right?
I see through that
Always still
Yeah
Art Bandalay.
What happened?
He's using your pictures as a profile photo.
Who?
Art Bandalay.
Art Bandalay, what does it say?
Where is he at?
Is this picture of you under his...
Is that you, or is it...
Let me...
Can you show what it...
What it's showing?
Because I can't see it.
Is it in the comments, or is it...
Or is it backstage?
Yeah, can I see it? Let me let me see what you're seeing. I'm not on discord, okay?
That was like I remember you're saying oh, you know like the pampers the art vandal a and then I
Just came across then okay, so oh guys by the way. I already did my discord like
Really cool. It's like
okay so uh i'd like to go to my uh friend
is he my friend i don't i don't even know if he's my friend on it but
okay are you my friend oh wait there we go
Let's make this
What happened it looks like this I'm gonna share the screen real quick
Tire screen
You see a screen
Yeah, that's me. Yeah, he's using my picture. Yeah using my picture
Yeah
Yeah, Art Mandalay, he's a he's a troll. He's a troll from I knew him for years. He's a doctor. He's
He's a he's a trover. He's like RG. That's what that's who Art Mandalay is. He's a he's another RG. That's all he is
Like I was like, is there anybody I would never like have as a mod and I would never have somebody
That doxed me as a mod and I would never have anybody that was actively attacking
Even somebody I really didn't like those activities like unless they were you know, I guess
Yeah, um, there's a guy AMC was the first person she's saying hi to in her chat. Oh, yeah, she embraces them bro
She loves them. He's part of the grease bro. She loves the grease bro. Like they invaded her bro
They got Janet they recently got Janet too like she betrayed groovy Jimmy and she
Completely went for the grease. She went for our G are all these guys like she completely they bought her they bought her out
So, I don't know what's going on. I don't know what they threatened her with but they got her
Yeah
I mean even like I mean RG
I mean RG could have
Amc working from a home point and amc docs all three of us Janet Vita and I like
earlier this year. Yeah
But RG didn't dox me like on his show, but he did a whole thing on Vita
Yeah
I don't know. It's just weird. It's just I don't understand why it's like well like the whole thing like I say, bro
There's a lot of like they call me they call a lot. You know, you heard that word a flip-flopper, right?
Yeah, so right now there's a lot of flip-floppers as far as like modding
There's a lot of mods that are flip-flopping. I remember when I showed you like what time was doing with sweepy and
You know, there's a lot of people that are doing stuff that you know
Don't normally you approve of and you know the mod, you know, you shouldn't really be doing
But I've been noticing that so I don't know if they're gonna be even more coming out as of late because I've been seeing a lot of people switch up
like
And then there's a whole, you know, I saw Bita was like doing a live show, and it was about, you know, it was a title that was something that I thought it was, but I was like, oh, I bet it was name to me.
And it was, because I talked to somebody we all know named Tracy, right?
Yeah.
Not Tracy X, it's Tracy.
Is that the other one? The Bita Tracy?
Yeah
Yeah, yeah, what is it the $800 that he didn't pay back. Yeah. Yeah, I know who that is
yesterday. I'm not, it's not like a secret. I was, it's like, because it's like, I knew Tracy would
just go behind my back and like, just give all my messages to Bita, like, right? Because it's like,
yeah, yeah. She did that before when I told her, hey, I'm being harassed and, like, by people coming
to my house and Ron's words about to do a panel on me, and then she went and participated in the
panel. So I was like, oh, yeah. Yeah, she was cheering them on and she was letting it happen.
Like, you know what? I said, I said, I said, you know, I felt like she misjudged me, and then she was like, oh, well, you know, I mean, it's like, I'm not gonna like, I don't know if I should have a home message. But anyway, like, basically, then I was like, well, you know.
I told her some of the fucked up shit that's happening and stuff like that, and she's like
what?
And she kind of like was like, oh, no, she's like, I'm just doing my own thing.
Like you're, you, you've hurt everybody that like like yours is about money and blah, blah,
blah, blah, all this stuff.
And so I was like, oh, and then it's like, then it's like, so she's like, oh, this one's
interfering with my friends, like my friends, like, and like, you know, just top it, it's
Do the beat us started all of this shit, bro all of this shit started been beat a drill line
Oh, yeah, you try to run she try to run your show tell you what to do
She try to tell you who to have who not to have who to block who to mod everything
It's like if it was her, so she tried to make it her secondary home
Right and it's like
And then she would also like not she wasn't very like I
Thought she was very nice until like you know the whole like
But she was like low-key like always like doing a sneak this I like it's like going back on that's why she was like
don't look at your
Old panels or don't play replays or anything or don't do clips or shorts
Yeah, cuz she don't want you to see it
She don't want you to see it with a clear vision with a different set of eyes like a
Because I never heard anybody else say, oh, don't do this on your channel, and like, why is it, like, I don't know.
No, play all your content. It's your content. It's your show. You can play as many times as you want. You own it.
We participate in your show. Once we do that on YouTube rights, if we read it in the terms of services,
we sign over rights to you and let you show our likenesses and our images and everything about us, because we sign on to that.
Streamyard we're agreeing to be on your show and release liability of our likeness
And you can show it as many times as you want and do what you please with it. It's your it's your video your show
And I don't want to like harp on her
it's like it makes it seem like I'm like a bully or something like that but I'm
like it's like it's just been totally misrepresenting I never did any I was
just like I was on walk basically walking on eggshells around her like
trying not to get her every time she would call it would be like yelling at
me you're on Kate's channel you know this person has a mug you're played this
clip it's like every time I was like just so negative and and it's like
I bet she has, like, okay, well, I can think, I don't need anything, though.
Oh, bro.
What happened?
Bro, that's bad, man.
That's so bad.
Dude, she would tell you like that?
Oh, yeah, she would call me all the time and it was like ever since like the like, um, you know
She would like yeah
I'm like, everyone else always does a real tarot.
I'm just like something like the star of life.
Yo, Psyche.
Psyche, Joe Shippley.
I'm bringing Joe Shippley to your show.
Bring him on.
You know what I mean?
Joe Shippley, the gay guy from, the gay guy from,
what's it called?
Yeah.
The gay dude from Baltimore.
Shout out to him.
Baltimore, Maryland.
I love you so much, I love you so much, I love you so much, I love you so much, I love you so much, I love you so much, I love you so much, I love you so much, I love you so much, I love you so much, I love you so much, I love you so much, I love you so much, I love you so much, I love you so much, I love you so much, I love you so much, I love you so much, I love you so much, I love you so much, I love you so much, I love you so much, I love you so much, I love you so much, I love you so much, I love you so much, I love you so much, I love you so much, I love you so much, I love you so much, I love you so much, I love you so much, I love you so much, I love you so much, I love you so much, I love you so much, I love you so much, I
Can you stay in neutral because it's like yeah, I haven't talked to you about some of the things that happened, okay, and I think you might
Is that your
shit Joe you don't scare nobody Joe you don't scare anybody
you're not scared, I am twice as scary as you
I am two times your size Joe
I am two times your size
you're looking like a fall fiction psyche, you're looking good with the glasses
you're looking like fall fiction man, just don't kill us
I don't know, this is not, this can't be the real ghost, is this you back stage?
You're looking as sick as ever, you fucking gay bitch.
I know.
Tell him.
Hey, hey, Joe.
Go suck on what he's doing.
It makes them more weirdo.
If you own more than one t-shirt, J-Dog always wears the same red t-shirt, like they can change your clothes, they're both.
Same red, what are you talking about?
This is orange, I have like three of these same colors in here, J-Dog.
I can smell you from here.
I have three of these colors, what are you talking about?
They're three different shades.
This is not even red, you're color blind.
Not easy.
I actually haven't thought about it.
That's racist and you make fun of a brother of mine brother.
This is not red.
This is orange.
Actually, he's telling him now, he's like, just come on in my house, right?
So people are actually like trying to open my door.
I'm not insulting everyone.
Yo, Psyche, if I pull up to your house, would you let me in?
I
Was knocking on the door, and I was like please open the door. I'm hungry, and I haven't
I'm odd on the street, and I'm eating raccoons
I'm putting cardboard on a grill
Shout out to you
Yeah, you said prairie page you said psycho that shit was funny low-key
She said psycho. That's funny the thing about psyche. He doesn't do weird shit without permission
Shout out to him
300 kilograms
Oh, Joe, and I'll be having gay sex together.
What?
I'm a regular.
Why is everyone turning gay?
Like, I was at this guy Vader's chat,
and he was like, I don't need to dance in this game.
He's cool now, psyche is trendy.
that's right. Yeah, it's
it's all gay, man. Thanks a
lot. I'm gonna be straight.
You know what, guys? I just
looked at my demographics.
80% of my audience is now male
and it's like the 25 to 34
demographic, which is a good
demographic, but then it's like
it said 75% are not subscribed.
What? They're not subscribed.
How do they know all we are?
Because
Where's your boyfriend at Joe, where's your boyfriend your boyfriend Joe, I know I mean I'm psyche
Would you consider to have Joe as a boy friend?
Like, God made you.
I don't think so.
God made you.
He was a boy friend of you.
But he made you Joe.
God made you Joe.
He's right now.
Joe's cute, but it's like, you know, Chris K, Joker, you know.
Who would you have?
Oh, yeah.
Chris K, you have Joker.
Who else?
Tony, the conductor, he's a stalker.
Who else is a stalker?
They're saying you live in a homeless shelter today, dog,
is saying that I'm not saying it but I don't know how I'm gonna find Joe's house
the
Hey, Joe, I think you gotta get him popping, bro.
You know what, Joe?
Joe, you gotta get him popping, bro.
I think that's a problem.
You gotta get it popping, homeboy.
You gotta get it popping.
You don't know how to get it popping.
No, you don't know how to get shit popping.
You don't know how to get shit popping.
That's where you should be on the panel with us.
You should be locked away.
You don't know how to get shit popping.
It's great.
We need a free jacket, but we're not paid.
You know what, Sikely, I think we gotta get him popping, bro.
We gotta get Joe popping, for sure.
Yeah, it's not gay, we gotta get him poppin',
take that, take some of his mother fucker off.
Well, let's dig, dig, we're gonna get him poppin' sick?
I think we should get him poppin' sick for Joe Shipley here.
You think so sick like say what about cable panel wanna make the executive decision and like we go to get you pop it
300 that your wife's cabinets, why don't you get a job and stop living off your wife?
You fucking nice hair cut by the way nice bangs. Oh
I
Have great hair. What are you talking about? We love psyche hair
I had psyche's hair. I would only we wish we could have psyche's hair, bro. I'm not blessed like psyche
I wish I could say my hat has the same size as my hair or my skull.
That's what I do with it.
Yo, pull up your hat, Joe.
Pull your hat up, Joe.
You really, you know, I don't really, I don't really like it in my head.
Or it's like, maybe you should take a side, but it's like, you don't want to stand up.
So you're really in there.
You're sitting in there.
I don't know for hours that you're like, why me?
I don't know.
Man.
I'm going to also shit, too, like, I don't know, I think, like, you know, you know what's
up turned against me thinking that I'm like
Hackin Vita or squeepee or Tracy or all these people and it's like I haven't
Hey psyche you came out swinging with your new channel people are really
Stay stay humble stay humble psyche don't let these fools trying to fold you shit. That's for sure
Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. I'm trying my best. Um, and I'm happy with, like,
I think that I'm getting a even better audience right now than I was getting on my,
my actual other channel. So it's like, it's probably better.
Climbing the mountain ain't easy, my boy.
Psyche, can I ask you a question, Psyche? I have one question, Psyche.
I might have asked you a question, but I forgot.
Name down your fucking business, bitch.
It depends.
I'm not sure.
It depends on the mood.
It depends how you're feeling.
OK.
All right.
I mean.
Now he's like saying, oh, you know, I paid $10.
And then he's like, you know, acting like I extorted him
for $10 or something like that when it's like.
No, no.
You just had to pay a fine.
I think you're going to get real nasty.
There you remember one night there was a freak card up here called 300 you remember the other dumbass
Yeah
I mean, it's like they go a little bit hard sometimes, but it's like they basically have
good hearts.
Don't ever say my name with Alex's name ever again, don't put us in the same place.
Well, I mean, I'm just saying you guys have both been really loyal to the show.
I'm literally...
It's not in a negative way, it's not in a negative way, my friend.
They're not you they're probably not here you're you're here. You guys are here, right? So yeah, we love psyche. We love me psyche
We support psyche. I wouldn't be for yourself
No, no, don't go against him. He's a leader psyche's a leader here. So don't go against psyche
We love you we love you
We do love psyche we do love psyche
We love Psyche, yes, yes, we love Psyche, yes, 100%.
I went yeah, and I want to like really yearn for you
I don't really believe it's like a religious move. I mean, it's like it is like a show, but it's not like
I'm asking you to like, you know, sell our possessions and like, you know, move to a compound. You can if you want
Satire on a Saturday little Saturday satire
Shut up.
Speaking of satire, just looking at J-Dog is satire.
Like, I'm so glad when I was born, wasn't born to me.
Why don't you turn your camera back on?
Why don't you turn your camera back on, Joe?
Turn your camera on instead of being a pussy-ass bitch.
And over here talking about me.
Turn your camera on.
There you go.
Yeah, yeah.
Let me just let you know.
Leave it on.
There you go.
Leave it on, Joe.
Leave it on.
There you go.
Hell yeah.
Joe, I wasn't like, I wasn't like, I wasn't like,
That's how we that's how we that's how we do it, Joe
Everybody camera on go she got a turn your camera on bro
You even if
There you go, I got you
Run one
You should be kicked off the panel time for not turning the camera. You should be kicked off. You should be kicked off the panel, boy.
Alright, dumbass. Don't be kicked out for being weird.
So I want to get rid of him real weird, I'll tell you, and look at him, look at him, look at him, look at him, look at him, look at him, look at him, look at him, look at him, look at him, look at him, look at him, look at him, look at him, look at him, look at him, look at him, look at him, look at him, look at him, look at him, look at him, look at him, look at him, look at him, look at him, look at him, look at him, look at him, look at him, look at him, look at him, look at him, look at him, look at him, look at him, look at him, look at him, look at him, look at him, look at him, look at him, look at him, look at him, look at him, look at him, look at him, look at him, look at him, look at him, look at him, look at
the
I
Shoulders
Is the microphone better do you hear me now guys? I'm sorry I finally got a working
Yeah, you're good
Dang, it's the mic is that
$100 right now, I'll show my face completely
To see this ugly to space I'd rather get
A-0-3 a-0-4 they're like that's the wrong password
I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't
All right, go ahead Paige. Come on. You're the
Out to you
A lot of yeah, I mean it's like there are flip-floppers and it's because I think it's because it's like there's like
So it's such a diverse community that sometimes people get along sometimes they don't you never know
What's what day it's gonna be with some people right or you know, there's a lot of drinking involved and drama
People mad about this person like I got really annoyed with today is like the person is like well
You heard all these people what I was like
You're not supposed to say oh, I heard all these people like you're not in those relationships. Those are my individual
Money to tell them what to do
I never want to be
If you got 75 cents to don't they get the fuck out of here we we big money over here
We want the big beam. You want to talk big money. It's like go ahead and talk remember ghost over remember
You really want to talk about Big Muffin?
Yeah, I remember Ghostober.
That's like the little smokey text.
It was long ago.
It was like we're all the faggots out there.
Yeah, Bob never goes sober.
It should be called GameTuber, actually.
GameTuber is a faggot sober.
Well, Ghostober was a faggot.
Ghostober was a really bad way of doing it.
I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't
Okay, you saw him you saw him one time on a beat his panel. Oh my god ghost. You're on beat his panel candle
Well, he came up here once I think because uh
We accused him of being Tony and so he like
He came on to prove he wasn't
You look like salmon
Cheers. I was looking at you with Sam at the same time. I was looking at both of you. Hey, I see him. I saw his eyes. I saw his eyes.
You see him guys?
This nigga looks like the Undertaker.
See ya!
It's kind of cute, but it lies on that but you're all retarded
There's a guy saying how yes, he's getting drunk as shit. Fuck you say you get drunk to the day comes
Take a little water
Stop being I'll fuck with six. They don't give a fuck. You'll get drunk to the cows come home. Oh damn it
the
Well, I did a Speedo show on Lord Vader's stream today and he kept encouraging me to like
Dance and strip and stuff and then
the
I need more, like, sexy outfits, because I feel like I'm just gonna open appeal pods.
You got most in.
Thank you. I feel like it's being in Chippendales dance on my stream. Maybe I'll get better tips. You're a star
I just need some like, you know
Hey, what's up? What's up?
Hey, now. Hey, now.
You're an all-star. You came on.
It's by, uh, what?
It's by the Heidi's baby. Heidi's baby.
I know it's on. I know it's on.
It's on. It's on.
You're an all-star, you're a bitch.
That's not how it works, you're a bitch.
Fuck off.
That's when Nickelodeon, Nickelodeon was just about to go to Universal Studios.
Nickelodeon was the spot to go to Universal Studios.
Oh, fuck yeah.
Every day after fucking Frost.
I remember when, like, I got, I got cable for the first time.
I was so excited because there was a show called...
Let me see
And then are you afraid of the dark
After midnight late tell it to you like after hours or tell it to you in red show or whatever it was called
They had like quads and a bunch of stripper Ella and shit like that on it
Oh
Night with Rhonda shear and it was all like bikini car wash, but it was like the dumbest like
Yeah, it was like vice cops. What do you what is that that looks like? Okay? Yeah, you're drinking some
Hey pages right there, bro. You could talk to her stop being
Permission don't fog. Okay. Thank you permission
And I permission to call
Sorry about that, sweetheart
Yeah, that was kind of a time that you didn't see that, but what is that?
Brute cologne? Oh, it's a fucking bag of rice. Yeah.
I
See tricks here. I'll do a trick. Show me a trick
It's tricks
Cuz I was gonna show you a trick, but I guess my trick is different than a trick
I'm gonna show you a trick. Oh, I see it. I want the magic
Yeah, oh look at that. He didn't make that disappear. What is that? Oh, yeah?
Look at him spritzing up he's spritzing up saying you know
Guys he's
it's like it's like it's like it's like it's like it's like it's like it's like it's like it's like it's like it's like it's like it's like it's like it's like it's like it's like it's like it's like it's like it's like it's like it's like it's like it's like it's like it's like it's like it's like it's like it's like it's like it's like it's like it's like it's like it's like it's like it's like it's like it's like it's like it's like it's like it's like it's like it's like it's like it's like it's like it's like it's like it's like it's like it's like it's like it's like it's like it's like it's like it's like it's like it's like it's like it's like it's like it's like it's like it's like it's like it's like it's like it's like it
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, 10, 10, 11, 12, 13, 14, 15, 16, 17, 18, 19, 20, 21, 22, 23, 23, 24, 25, 26, 27, 28, 29, 30, 31, 31, 31, 31, 31, 31, 31, 31, 31, 31, 31, 31, 31, 31, 31, 31, 31, 31, 31, 31, 31, 31, 31, 31, 31, 31, 31, 31, 31, 31, 31, 31, 31, 31, 31, 31, 31, 31, 31, 31, 31, 31, 31, 31, 31, 31, 31, 31, 31, 31, 31, 31, 31, 31, 31, 31, 31, 31, 31, 31, 31, 31, 31, 31, 31, 31, 31, 31, 31, 31, 31, 31, 31, 31, 31, 31, 31, 31, 31, 31
the
That is my smoke hookah with my girl. That's how she looks. Yeah
That thing is that your new profile
animated and it was like oh this is against TOS or like it was against that they were like it was too
She's like smoke or something that should be against TOS. It should be but it's just it could be tobacco smoke
She's been smoking a hookah. Okay. I'm six three
the
I
Make sure the word
This is thinking about you make sure to tell them that all right
Wow imagine thinking about us imagine like thinking about us. I think about you
I mean, you know, I think about you. I think like what's my voice sig doing? That's my fucking real ojik a boysig
Well, I mean sing I don't sing for fucking way too long wait
Where he's doing that on purpose he thought man. Oh, you do like it. Sorry about that. Whoa, hey, just like how do you're
Kim just asked me she got
W
Come on, come over to the show Kim. I can be your boss. Look at this. Hey, go tell your
Shut up to eat on you some more. Why are Fridge look shut down?
Why are you fucking?
They're not
You soulless motherfucker
Saturday Saturdays
the
that's why you were scared to buy a heck out of it but I like it like this right you were you were scared to buy a hector bro
yeah you look like a halloween pumpkin halloween's over nigga turn your camera off
I'm gonna do what hector did to iBBD
I'm gonna call you up like a cackle man
I'm gonna be scared to come back
oh my god it's tough
you guys really don't know bro
go ahead Ty let Ty say something
go ahead Ty
How about this the spooky enough that's why are you a creep on a leash? Oh
What happened? Oh
Well, I
It's all right. It's all right. Give me that. All right. Oh, there you go. Hold on. Oh, look, it's a full screen.
Oh, it's on stage. It's your show. Shout out to you. Yeah. I'm gonna take a shot. Cheers.
Take a shot. Take a shot. Go ahead. Take a shot. I can't come around.
It's really his hoax. Fuck you, bro. Shout out for you, underwatcher. Take a shot. You fucking faggot. Go ahead.
I already did.
Already did
Well, I didn't take a shot then shut the fuck up. I don't think you're two percent
He said I don't care if people say that word because usually the most people are like half gay. Anyways, yeah
of the
one of the
the
Yeah, and you won't make a soundboard on the you sound you won't even make you
So, you know
Everybody wants to be something in LA right? Yeah in LA for sure. It's hard. I mean
And that's like really competitive and everyone's all chasing the chasing money and everybody's chasing the money, bro, right?
Fucking kills, right? It's like if you meet somebody that's more sober than you. Oh, you're gonna go to war for sure
You do everyone's fucking on something out here, right?
I know general managers they take out a wrong shit
Well, I'm like, I'll be clowning them cuz I I hang out with them. I'll be like might not go pop into the let's go
Drink some coffee dog. Oh, no. I'm already off this Adderall pill
Stupid as that's how I beat them. That's how I get them. I don't take
You wait until a day they pass out or something. I
Have to crash out and burn out. I'm like, let's go drink some coffee my boy. Let's go
I'm trying to show my face. Can I get guys to drink coffee in a bag?
A lot of people don't drink coffee in a bag.
They're on medication.
All right, let's go drink some coffee boy. Let's go drink a coffee boy. Yeah, you're scared to drink a coffee boy
Because you probably
I am scared to drink coffee with you. I'd never go over your ass
Hell no, I'm scared to say it
Damn right I'm scared. I live out here. I see these people
I don't see you. I live on the street boy. I live on the street
I'm trying to show my face real quick
the
are you committed
Yes, but you still are
The reason you don't want to show your head swallowing three times the size of a normal versus that yes, but this guy looks like
My dad taught me not to hide from people. Yo, are you single?
Yes
No, are you single nobody cares if you take your vote off like what do you say we're gonna
There's a guy in the chat
Don't we know what yes, I ain't
Well, it's up to you psyche psyche am I single or am I not because I thought me and psyche had something going here
Like am I single or am I not psyche? It's up to you then tell him
Moving out of your house, I'm never coming back because I've you bad fucking I'm not sleeping
I
Get fish tacos over there all the time. Yeah drunk. Oh, and the karaoke
Every year up we can hang out in a week. I live right just walking distance
I mean, I'm like 10 minutes away from here. 10 minutes away. I'm always there. I love her talk
Yeah, yeah, better
Veterans Park is so chill
Maybe you gotta be me and my girl and my cats and shit, but I like drinking and shit, you know, I dream
Yeah, I am actually
the
Yeah, and now it's clipped
Peter was and then and then Ziggy started to ask you and then
Don't start doing it till they don't pay I know
It was like it was okay because I was like, you know
Oh
Shit look at my ring was so tight look at how good my ring into my finger was so tight
Yeah, that's a really tight
Conflicts where you wear the cock ring. Wow, man. I can't use it as a cock ring. It's too small
But I can make, I can probably this one because it has like a, it's like, you know, I like these rings that are like have an open, you can stretch them out and stuff.
I could probably fit my dick through that.
Sorry about that.
In my balls.
Saiki, about that line.
That was a joke, guys.
Go boy now. Who's laughing at that? You creep.
Hey Saiki, hey, can you let me wear the glasses when we meet up?
I
Like those pink ones
I like to get cheap glasses that usually is like sit on them
that's cool there's some cool shit in there you know what you're doing that's a cool stuff
and the rings too all the rings i got like i mean i someone some of these i paid a little more
but these rings are like i'll be there as a community weekend i guess
y'all look at his knuckles they got a fucking old set of rings let's do it let's do first stream
I'll pay a torrents. I'll pay the top call shit. Let's go hang out. I was born in torrents. Yeah
What the fuck? It's kind of getting a little creepy up in here. Oh, so you're from the hood. You're a hood boy
San Pedro, I know people, you know, I was like, I've lived in San Pedro for a little bit. I uh,
Yeah, San Pedro is bad. I've hit it in the hard harbor city
And I know Rob
I got that. You know, you know. Damn, bro. Let's go to the top, bro.
We'll set this shit up. We'll first set this shit up.
For sure.
Cheers to you.
Wow, man.
The glasses go on.
But those here, they ain't Cartier. The pink ones, the other one.
They ain't Cartier.
Yeah, did you want to be
You know most of the classes are made of the same
like they're made in the same factories is like
designer one
where about the just go up maybe we're neckline this Mount Everest like nothing bro
down a plane California mean I was lucky next weekend already got a plane ticket out there where do you
it's like I can do it
it's so close to me though that's what I'm saying
I know I kind of knew we were like kind of close but I knew you were like I used to LA or LA but
I don't want this fucking thing
of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of
It's with you and like cut his hair like is he really does need a haircut romance. It's like if you meet up with 300 do me a favor
Two weeks I get a haircut every week
Hey, hey, do you ever see apocalyptico like with milk in the Mel Gibson directed it? It's like in like in like
It's about South America and like
Yes, yeah
Like I noticed like that's a popular haircut now like
Where you get paid up here, you look like you're an army nigga or something, like an army guy.
That one time when I fucking face 300 go. Oh, I'm sorry. I don't want to get violent
I don't make friends that is rude. See why do I got to be like that?
It's fucking why you gotta be having that job. That's what I'll be taught. I'll be taught you to be a big all the way
So rude right now
I'll be taught you to be a big but doesn't know how to be humble
Oh, tell me the best all these my fucking
Image I made
you know that can hang that on my wall that could be on the mother that's that could be a poster in and like five
Actually frame that and kiss it every day when I wake up for work like this. Yeah, this is multi-cultural shit right here
This is the day before work. I want to give it a little bit. I was like
Hey psyche, I'll buy a shot psyche. Oh cool. Yeah
I
Who is that that? Oh, that's Alexander Mayer's on page. She came out and we went to dinner
Recently already come by a month ago and then
This I read on the beats
Yeah, I'm sure we're crazy
And here's how this is all
original
It's like
Thank you, babe. Thank you, babe. Sorry that was showing off
Went to dinner at this talk was at this dinner. It was really good. There we are. Oh
where was that?
It's called the Hudson House.
We went to the Hudson House, which is like
Virginia by me, and it's like, I had fish tacos.
They ever done that?
Oh, all right.
Yeah.
I think we're, we have the same birthday, and I think we're planning on
getting to where she hugs you.
That's the same birthday.
Yeah.
We're the god.
He's not even.
I have this picture.
Hold on.
This is funny.
Because I was trying to do like, I was like,
trying to do like a friendly animation with it.
But it kind of like, let's see.
Let me see.
Where is it?
That's right.
Psyche.
I knew you was a real one, bud.
Shut the fuck up, boy.
Oh, I'm blue.
Oh, fuck.
I can't say no to this.
Let me see this again. I said Eskimo kiss. You want to see it again? Hold on. Yeah
Eskimo kiss is where you know you get it
That's actually give me a burner actually anybody else got a burner
No, I didn't get on the owner. That's his owner. I don't know what but you're talking about you being weird
I guess that's what I'm talking about.
He can't even let the army get the pussy.
I didn't base him, but it's actually that's the guy.
Let the army get the pussy.
He got it.
Why are you being all weird about it?
I'm not being weird. I just see my best friend's kiss on the lips
It was Alex it's like
Tendencies
Did not turn you over you do not
it's because we're just
let me know if there's anything else you'd like to adjust before creating it
this is where we are but
fuck the bullshit
hey
we're in a cult guys
I don't know if you guys know it or not
but I'm pretty sure we're in a cult
Yeah, and don't I mean some people are afraid. I think it's a it's like basically we're it's like a family
Right like not like the Manson family, but like
Cheers
I'll tell you what it's like
For like three days straight, that should would have been gone in my house for sure
But you don't even drink you don't drink half gallons you drink leaders
This is a half gallon
You're stupid and shit
That's why you all fucking dumb
Oh, yeah, congratulations all stupid and shit shout out to you
Shout out to you
You're due to your duties to your family
My personal time to handle my family to shout out to you
You know like Nike set up to fucking Nike sponsors like
Shut up to you my boy
the
You three are the same. What are you gonna do about it, boy? No, I'd slap you three are the same. What are you gonna do about it?
Well, you pay her right or what? Why is she all mad at you all the time? Why is she hitting you?
Let's get to the bottom of this.
Break your leg. Break your fucking back.
She's putting hands on you. Why are you exposure off her?
He will be next week.
He will be rolling around in a wheelchair.
I'm going to be rolling in a wheelchair, boy.
That girl's going to have to see you around.
I'll be seeing that shit, and that should be funny.
I'll be watching you.
I'll be watching you, bro.
I'll be laughing.
I'll be like, damn, I'll be feeling sorry for you sometime.
I'll be like, why you do that?
What the fuck, bro?
But who am I, huh?
Who am I to say anything?
You can keep getting smacked up like you like it.
Go ahead, bro.
Go ahead, bro, it's none of my business.
You get smacked around, you get shatty, you shatty, boy.
What's the problem if you talk to?
Because you may be strapped in a wheelchair the next time
you ever fucking talk to me like that.
Yeah, right, man.
You scared a heck of me.
That's my cousin, bro.
You know, heck, there's my cousin.
You want to do it?
I'll fucking break you.
Heck, there's my cousin, bro.
the
guy guys
a little bit
I
Would fucking lift Alex up off the ground
Why are you like why are you lifting me up and carry me Alex just be quiet? I'm carrying you you never gonna walk again, baby
I'm gonna carry you where you
Wait, these skinny ass girls be with Alex Myers
look at Trisha, she all looking like they're friends now
they're friends, they're all looking like sticks and shit
she's a vampire cat, she's black
she has big ass booty, big ass tail
don't ask where she is, she's a fucker
isn't she in playboy?
she was in playboy, right?
she was in playboy
shit
i know if you playboy, if you playboy
holy shit
shut out there
Hey, I was on Trace's dream and she started stripping for us. She was stripping for me and sick
Don't be I don't condone that shit, but I was drunk and she was drunk and that shit happened
Alex mayors breath
Am I am I muted or you guys hear me?
Lucid dance from a playboy bunny. How many people could say that?
exactly now you're right for real 300 I know I'll fuck with you but you're right for real to be a playboy bunny
It takes like one-on-one man. It's only if you can't become a playboy bunny
Duh, you just can't wait. It's like a different thing now. Now. It's all the internet stuff. And so it's like
Think of all the whores that wanted to be playboy bunnies
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
the
the way I wear my hat
And the West Coast is the best coast
Tell you that really bad
The best coast the East Coast is the real shit boy
What are you saying, that's the worst when I go to Michigan, you're the one being racist when I pull up to your
You be racist
that up
that's not just me
LA are really racist because there's like
so like it's like a huge
it's like so integrated
why are black
yeah
over it nigga
nobody's coming to visit you
shout out to you
I mean
and I see Joe
Oh
Playing that crash the other day then go
Joe are you near good times?
Shut up to you. I
He's like so
bottles or something like that for a living in Michigan. He has a scam or something. I don't know
For the episode you ever see Seinfeld's psyche. Yeah
Good times has garnered enough clout that he has enough lonely desperate housewives in his life
Good times are racist and shout out to him though. I mean don't hate the player
The Kansan is a mail truck
And like took in the Michigan, but I've heard I don't know if it's true
I don't want to talk shit on good times, but I've heard and maybe a rumor
Keep like
Every kid so you collect like 20 cans that's two bucks. So
With that your pipe is smelly
Well, what am I putting in my pipes of smoke Joe?
Oh, what if he collected 5,000 cans in Minnesota?
Remember when people called money bones like hey, I got three bones for you. I mean, I was called
He also called dominoes bones, right? Yeah, I guess are you two dominoes, man? Are you two domes? I
Like this one
Stay right there. That's all of it
Hold on
It's supposed to be
Like it
One day and then you peel entitled
Say
So you don't buy the next one right now to that
Well, it's not acting no hard because I'm not coming at you like that
That's me don't have a little bone at it up because I still got
This is a problem my girl my girl thing. I don't got it like
the
all the way you have to wait the money the way the money for me
the way the money for me
all the fucking
I got more motion
that's why me and Psyche you really get along
they don't understand that
he understands
what am I saying
what does he understand
Psyche my girl said
she fucks with you and we probably have a threesome
we're gonna have to
shout out to you
but she's gonna
Hey people that like that know about sex know about sex. That's it
That's all I gotta say
See people are talking about sex like 300 never had sex like people that are like
That's what
of the
the
I tried them, they were fucking terrible
So what do you say?
I'm just telling, what I'm saying is that they don't sell this shit after midnight
That's what I'm telling you
You can't get chicken strips in the middle of the night
I know this shit, I'm just saying
What other time?
let me ask you a question what other time do you want to eat chicken strips in LA you could get
besides the middle of the fucking night yeah you can yeah i mean i could go to 711 and get them
and they suck over here they had a couple you know what i mean i think one of the best places
around here is like a taco truck up the street that parks in the parking lot well yeah yeah you
Go off to the top of truck
You don't see that's what I'm saying
These LA niggas are sheltered, but you're sheltered
You're surrounded by beiners, you don't even know what how all means
Means it's blessed, right? You don't even know you don't even know what hello means
You're all sheltered and shit, but you're surrounded by beiners
You're surrounded by beiners
You'd be surrounded by beiners, but you're all sheltered and shit shout out to you
Shout out to you. Oh beiners and black people shout out to you stupid ass retard
Shout out to you. You don't know what hello food is
It means it's
You're all fucking dumb and shit
We know we know that you know, okay, what I'm saying is that 300 glow does not know
300 glow doesn't know what hello for this shout out to him. He's all shelter. He lives in the shelter
He lives in a geltic gated community
You know
He lives in a gated community. He's all sheltered and she's shot out to him
Bring it shout out shout out to you bro. Shout out to you
was also are now shot out to you over a shot out to you was he was he you get
that up real quick for you and say say go probably beat the shit out of you 300
yeah I was talking about this thing a four foot tall
I'll stomp on that
that was my boy
that nigga my new yorker that's why he got so tough
you know what I'm saying New York
New York is next to you
And LA people are just trying to have fun
Like fucking little gay surfers
Yeah, I got a way you can fucking catch
Locals only I believe in that shit
Locals only I really love leaving that shit and I protect that shit
that's how it was when I was in Palo Verde, it's like the people surfing was like so protected by the locals
they're like, we were like, we finalized everyone's car, that wasn't from them
either you're not from here, you're from Pocari
why are you here?
like, I mean it comes with the territory, like you're literally in
yeah, I come from New York to the Bronx to start selling shit, nobody would tell me
shout out to you bro
The Jaws well, we trying to do that shit will fuck is you we ain't never seen you around
I heard a cat like cry I where the god I heard a cat cry
Oh
Shout out to tricks
That's Lola sleeping back you're just in kind of oh, she's kissing him. Hey, Lola don't his to your son
she did. She actually like all her kittens survived. She had five kittens. They all survived and like with that as soon as they got a certain point, she started hissing at them and they would not want to do with them. But now she gets along with tricks. He's the only one that's sick around.
They don't play this.
Who do you think you are?
I just wanted to say, hey, Joe, hey, Joe.
Well, go ahead, 300.
Who do I think I am?
I think I'm the big dog.
He thinks he's a big dog.
Keep thinking that, my boy.
When you went to school, why did your boss shout out to you?
I don't think you were retarded.
Sorry about this.
300 glow used to go to school in the short bus.
Shout out to him
With people like you I'll be like these dumbasses really think they have a word to say
Let's get rid of the speech, but like you guys over here walking around like all stupid and shit
30 people and you want to be the smartest one, right?
right you're the smartest by the way
Frank I have an empty fucking E and J bottle, but you're the smartest one
You're gonna drive me to a liquor store
Joe I'm gonna order over
You're gonna pick me up in the escalate you have you got a big
Yeah
I'll tell you, if you ever spend a lot of shoes, let's send them to Uber and sale.
just to take me to the liquor store, that's like a block away, Joe's gonna pick me up in the black Estee La
and he's gonna open the door for me and be like, hello sir, how you doing?
and then I'm gonna go and then I'm gonna step into the black truck and he's gonna close the door for me
and then offer me some water, like you see what I'm saying, you guys really don't play
go on the bridge, mother, go alive, still talking to me
I'll cook you Joe, I'm sorry
Well, hey cook away
Do what you got to do, man. Do what you got to do cook away
Hey, um guys, I have the discord going to here's the link to the discord
You can just make sure you're signed up to that and then you'll never like lose me
And blow my brains out for I ever join your discord
I would literally
You can friend me on this court. You don't have to be on my in my server, but you can just run me
of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of
No, look in the, look in the chat. I know it's, I know it's Sharon, it's not good, but it's like,
actually it's pretty good for like, maintaining a community away from
Yeah, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, Sharon, it's not good, but it's like, actually, it's pretty good for like, maintaining a community away from
of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of
say it today on beat us. I did hear him say that was so rude.
Good times. Like she always was hilarious.
For duty. You good times.
What the fuck?
Keep talking about shooting people and stuff.
I mean, oh, no, what's that?
He times was saying, oh, and then she was like,
and she put it back stage and then she'd let her right back up.
I don't understand.
And then Sam is like,
I hold on. Let me show my camera. Look at my eye.
look at my elbows. For a good time, Bita and Sandan, that was a little too much. That was a little too far, SIG. SIG, you got to admit, even you got to admit SIG, that was a little too far.
What are you talking about?
I was talking about when good times went far with Bita. I've never heard Bita be rude to good times, not once in my life that I ever heard Bita be mean to him.
Never?
to take us back saying you go fuck yourself to you piece of shit
I don't remember this
well I do remember this
well remember this thing
fuck yourself remember that
I'll believe you
I will remember
I will keep this in mind
I'll keep this in mind thank you for reminding me
look at me shout out to you
this is the fucking most ugliest man
shout out to you
Good times was calling beat of this
Before and it was rude. It was fucking disgusting
Almost would the joy be this sit psyche your mouth is wide open. I'm just thinking out. You're a man. Yeah, but
Are you ending a straight wide no and everybody I banned everybody
Oh, is everyone is everyone gone from the chat? What's going on?
10 minutes ago. Oh
There's 15 people
There are there's yeah 15 people, you know last night there was 40 people and nobody was talking at all
I was like, oh, this is weird. I guarantee you out of the 15 people here 13 of them are gay
So a two people that are gay nice to meet you
Nice to meet you guys
Well, I get born my hair back into a ponytail I could pull it back. Is that what you want to do?
You want to show up your fucking hair?
I'm trying to like mama
Don't you tell me when I walk away? Oh, mommy remember that song by dancing. Hello. Yeah
Why is he wearing Jeffery Dobber sunglasses? Oh, my
These are my cold
Mommy
Now I'm a good buzz in a second figure. I haven't had a good time. I always appreciate when you let me own your streams
But you got to say one thing you are the gayest guy I ever met and that's a that's a compliment
It's actually a compliment man. I am
Care of me when you lick your chops. Sorry ciggies
You see another chance, I always like I give him a chance, but
I always give everybody a chance.
I always got respected by his psyche.
Whoa, God, those songs are terrifying.
Okay, let me fix this.
Okay, I got this, okay.
I think I can make this track now.
I think so.
Desktop, okay.
So, I have to read this music video real quick.
Whew, do you guys make music videos on?
Alexander's made some amazing AI music videos.
I wonder how much software she's used, so she's so good.
She has very realistic AI.
I made them so strong, and I didn't say,
I did wish, and I did say like I threatened Alexander
in a bad way, but I never meant it.
Come on, Alex.
You know how fucking fuck what Alex the best.
I just, maybe I was stronger than I said, like I'll kill her or something.
Oh, okay, yeah, really?
Yeah, of course you do not mean that, and, right, you apologize.
I'm not gonna kill anything.
Okay, well, you can kill my high.
No, it's good.
Kill the vibe.
Oh, that's me now.
Yeah, I like that, Suggie.
That was actually pretty funny.
You killed my, you got like a buzz kill.
That's pretty good.
Okay.
But this don't make me feel good.
Now, there's the waiters over.
Now, it seems like a, like a pretty good thing to say.
Okay, are you ready for a song?
You wanna see a video?
the
Well, I thought that thing that is was, you know, maybe like, getting in there and
Did things like he and I want to talk to you big though. I thought about like collecting something like getting like
You know, like physical media is dying like DVDs. I remember having like I used to love wrestling and I had so many wrestling DVDs
Like a hundred of them and then when they got peacock, they had the WWE Network
And I was like, oh, they have all wrestling on peacock. I just like I don't care about DVDs anymore
But now you never know what can happen in this world. So you got to have your physical. I got my favorite movie is ZT photos
Remember that what do you think?
Yeah, Drew Barrymore was an enemy, actually.
Hold on, one thing, Suggie, I want to say this to you.
Do you remember when E.T. was dead and the little kids' heart
like, come back to life and like, the flower like, grew?
That's one thing.
You're on the E.T. ride in Universal Studios,
and you get on like, a bike, and you go into like,
and it would just be like a roller coaster with a,
you're on the bike and stuff like that.
Oh no, one thing I asked you, do you remember Nickelodeon, the TV show, what would you do
when they had a pie machine and it would like fling flies, not flies, like it would fling
pies at your face from every angle, it would just like, oh, you got hit by from there,
a pie from there, like a pie right in the, like right in the fucking face.
And like the kids would be like, I love it.
Like, I just got hit with a pile of Nickelodeon.
I guarantee it.
Before that, it was a show called
You Can't Do That on Television,
and they would slime people.
What the fuck would you do?
But what would you do was like the more like our generation like it was I remember that when I first got cable
I was so excited to watch that show. It would be like Mark Summers in the audience, right?
He'd be like an audience
It's a rare condition this day
Any good you got it you have a cut it out
Have mercy
Have mercy Jesse Gonzales how rude
and a lot of stuff.
Oh, stop it.
What was that?
Hey, hey, hey Miss.
She was on me belt with Dorky and then she got real hot.
Remember?
Remember Michelle had like,
Stephanie had, hey, how rude or whatever.
And remember Michelle like...
Don't have a camera
Like a thing like remember DJ Tanner. She never like really had like a statement. No, she just had like a crisis every week
Like she'd be bulimic. She'd be shoplifting. She'd be like, you know
Where DJ was like on the treadmill and she was like they're like dad DJs get real skinny like she's like
out
Like damn fuck or he's like yeah, it's great. And then she like
passed out. Remember I'm saved by the bell when like Jesse Spano goes on like Adderall
and she's like, I'm so excited. I'm so excited. I'm so scared.
Remember when Deep Melo, remember when Stephanie backed the car through the kitchen window?
Like, I'm sorry about this. Sorry I parked the car.
Oops.
Uh, remember when they went to Hawaii and they like found these like manuhunes, which are like these like, uh,
The land and tj kept seeing steve like everybody she like thought she saw like turned into steve. Do you remember that? Thank you
And like
Yeah
Remember like Uncle
Uncle Joey had this like this like woodchuck Joe and it was like a he was like a famous celebrity and everyone knows in that house
Don't even talk to me don't say another word don't think of it
No, hold on. It was like, what are you the woodchuck or something?
It was one of the woodchuckers I get. Well, let me tell you one thing.
Remember the episode where Joey like went away and they made a room for Joey in the basement?
Remember they turn the garage? No, I'm not a lamp. It's like I'm talking to the series.
Yeah. Yeah. I remember that and Joey was all mad.
He was like, you guys don't even care about me. You don't love me.
like I'm left and you didn't even like call me or nothing and like Joey go
downstairs he's like why why don't want to go downstairs you don't love me
and then he went downstairs they turned the basement into his room he's like oh
I love you guys like you did this for me see that's what I I want to read that
Well, yeah, and remember like it was like the show was supposedly like started about like hurt their mom like died in the tragic accident and like
Like the uncles moved in and they nobody looks like anybody. I don't know who's supposed to be related to who like
Not to interrupt you and I do apologize. I know I talk a lot
There was one episode of Full House where they actually like were watching a video like they had a videotape and they watch and there's one episode
Where you actually see their mom?
There is one
Was that Danny's wife was Danny's wife
Let me take one last thing if you don't mind pink glasses guys
Remember when Jesse rode his motorcycle like on the ledge of a building like I'm dr. Death like I'm on the Jesse
I'm a whole I'm a crazy man
Like calm down Jess. You got children. Yeah, you got twins. Yeah, remember. Yeah, and then like Danny and like
Jesse's you know wife we're on the good morning San Francisco. We'll wake up San Francisco and
What was I'll give you a dollar right now, what was Jesse's twins name his two sons, what were the twins names?
I don't remember
Alex
Out to Nikki or something like that. You know, you can't remember wake up San Francisco. So that does count as something
And it was like
And then remember like I remember like there's one where it was like somebody's birthday and like they like
I forgot what happened, but it's like they didn't he didn't have a gift
Hawaii for Christmas and they got stuck at the airport and like then like someone's dressed up as Santa
Can I say one thing to you? I'm getting all excited
But do you remember the one episode where it was Kimmy Gibbler's birthday and DJ forgot Kimmy get they all forgot Kimmy Gibbler's birthday
And they tried to like make her like a fake tool of paper like wrap her gift into and Kimmy was like at first Kimmy loved it
But then after a while Kimmy was like hold on
You guys didn't even remember my birthday
And then like the sad music kicks in like Dan and like you didn't even fucking remember my birthday
you tanners
Do you remember when
Like he got he got DJ like a like a sweatshirt and then she like it got stolen or something
And so she went to a store and like stole the sweatshirt, but it had like the little
The tag and so she like had it all wrapped up and then they try to return it and they got caught returning it and like basically
Where Jesse like remember where they thought they stay somebody stole Michelle's bike and Jesse stole the bike and
Joe, we saw the bike and they all had the same bike like, hey, we all got the same fucking bike.
You remember that?
Yes or no?
Well, yeah, I do.
But Bob Sagan had a head injury for some reason.
He also was a really dirty comic.
Oh, that was the, no, that was the last I swear to God.
Let me tell you one thing.
It's like, if you don't mind, I know you always let me talk.
I appreciate you.
When I was in Boy Scouts and I was like 10 years old in 1995, I was 11 and I mean this from my heart
I remember telling my mom like this is the last episode of full house like fuck Boy Scouts mom
She's like yeah, we're going to
And I'm like no I'm not I'm staying home watching fucking last episode of full house
The last episode was it was a two-parter where like Michelle fell off a horse and like lost her memory
And they're all like telling her like member this member that
And then Michelle finally is like, I do remember that.
And then I cried, I was 11 years old,
that was the first tears I ever had.
Aw, that's so sweet.
I think I'm like, I don't know, I remember when they saw the Tiffany concert and like
there, it was like, I think we're alone, nah, that was the song they sang, it was in the
notebooks.
Remember the episode where Jesse took the people to the field trip and they knocked
the dinosaur bones down, like the dinosaur fell down, and like Jesse, like your group
is bad, Danny's group is good, like Jesse, your group knocked the fossils down.
Oh my God.
I haven't seen that show in years. Wow. That's a long time ago. Oh wait. I mean
I'll go to my fucking grave saying full house is the greatest TV show that I ever fucking loved
I fucking love full house
And you know what? I don't give a fucking to agree or not. It's like, you know, if I see you and I like you say
He agrees with me
Full house will always be my favorite TV show.
It's a recognition this day and age to read and oh, hold on.
Oh, yeah, on the newspaper, babe.
I'd like to hear whoever out of this world, do you ever watch that?
Evie?
it's the big
and they're like all in the convertible and stuff
that's fucking Danny back there talking about sweetheart
well
I'm going to hear a good song, I made a new song but it's kind of long let me see
okay let's see if this video will play, let's see
I won't let me join, see Bami earlier because I talked too much
you're fine, I think this will work
For the tail kicks off, let me confess my crime
I took what was mine, because time is fake
And the cosmos refuses to file proper paperwork
We weren't just friends, we were a whole curse to it
Waiting for the draw, and in true cult fashion
I built what the gods never dared draft
A love story held together
The day prophecy and questionable ethics
The fear got loud like trolls on a slow Tuesday
So I panicked, grabbed fate by the throat
And cut every possible future off at the source
Call it romantic, call it psychotic
Call it Saturday night at the pan over
She left so hard, she almost haunted herself
We don't count in the code, numbers are a mortal prison
Colder heart, I like it, was a limited edition merch
Drop her eyes when sunny side up
Eat it, eat it, eat it
Not my proudest moment, but lovers' quarrels get messy
When the water canals are tax-deductible
Make it romantic
The karma clocks in
The vengeful soul crawls back
From beyond the grave
Like, yeah, we're not done
Babe, possession, resurrection
A little light revenge
The usual cult of psychic Tuesday
She smiles wide enough to quality
across the veil to apologize like a man returning a late library book she burned
in hell while I lounged in heaven awkward gotta fix that imbalance before she
slaps me with a cosmic fire
Andromelius' best man, Lenore's flower, Kat Metandy, officiating with side-glance, Judgement.
Do you take this man in death for the rest of your wonderfully unnatural afterlife?
Cosmic slip up
Would be so chilly I'd need a heater for a ghostly thighs
But here we are, the fire dies
The story restarts and eternity smells
Painly of incense and bad decisions
Baby don't cry, everybody's gotta die sometimes
for supporting our extremely ill-advised union.
See you next time.
Then the hunger hits, that animal pulse we all pretend we don't have.
I lose control, taste it, apply.
Don't judge, and suddenly someone screams.
Everyone grows up eventually, and one of these nights,
yeah, I'll hunt again.
Well, I didn't really work out the way. There's sound effects there. Uh-oh. Hello?
The people that are like, hey, where'd everybody go?
I don't know. Get back up here, guys. There's how many people? 19 people in chat, though.
Well, let me call a signal. Let me call a signal. Let me call send us in a smoke signal for signal
That's right. There it is
Well, why are you doing that?
I just finished having sex, bro. Okay. Oh, you did. Yeah, cool. Let's see
Oh, I mean really?
Yeah
So here's my cults. This is my cult song
You're sick.
With super chat pricing
Just online
Cult
Corsaking
Yeah
Enlightenments, Merch, Size, Medium
We drink the algorithms, wa
Okay, oh shit.
Oh, that was my bracelet.
Okay, well, let's see.
Hi Chanel.
You've been to the house,
you looked up to the house of San Francisco.
I think, yeah, it's on the street call.
What's that street call in San Francisco
that it's real, like, windy?
Okay.
Whew.
Well, there's 13 people. Let me see. Why don't I make a few piles of cards?
I'll make three piles. Okay, and then you choose one two or three and
Every stack will have an interpretation. Okay, so I'm gonna do like actually four cards of a stack. Okay, so
Two three
Okay
You got the alien cards? Okay. One, two, three. Oh, okay. And I got this one.
This is fun. I haven't done these pick a pile before. I hear it might be a fun thing to do.
Because then everyone can participate. Everyone can still reading and then it's like I don't have to
Everyone it's kind of unique and individual and surprise
And then one more deck, okay
Eternity snows faintly of incense and bad. Yeah
Oh, do you see the, is that on one of my songs or is that on the website?
Hold on, okay, one, two, three.
Okay, so guys, pick a number between one and three
and let me know your number in the chat.
And I'm going to pull each, and here I'll show you that I have all the cards laid out.
Oh, here we go.
Oh, I need to fix the camera.
Green light on I'll turn it off
Let's see I've got to get this you know figured out like a little bit better. Okay, there we go. Oh my gosh
It's a little bit. It's not terrible. So you got these three piles. Okay, so tell me your tell me your pile
And
We'll uh
Go ahead. Okay. Yeah, we got 21. See I have to kind of my table's not that big of a mess. It's kind of a
kind of bad
Three, okay, Sharon says three.
I'll read three first, we'll figure that out.
Okay, so Sharon, we have perseverance.
Okay, we have perseverance.
This reminds me a lot of the strength card.
It's got that Leo energy and it's also like keep going.
And there's also going through a passage and stuff like that.
being supported in 2021?
Well,
How do I do that like that? Are we playing blackjack? I'm not sure. Oh, but this is and this card is number eight
So this is strength. That is the number eight card. It just reminded me of Leo energy and so that is the strength
Okay, so you've got this great inner strength whoever is the number three
Oh, you got the the chariot also moving forward successfully something got a beautiful horse there, too, okay?
And again, this the sun is shining above supporting your path on that one the alien card is
Justice, okay, this is Libra energy, but this is just this Justice card is
Well, it's not balance in the maintaining the balance of the universe, but also
Getting justice for yourself. Okay, two. Okay, number two. Okay, so we'll do two next. Okay, and then so that's the Justice card beautiful
Beautiful alien justice, probably the cutest alien in the deck. Oh, and then the Queen of Swords knowing what to cut out and what to keep
Okay, kind of being a little bit ruthless because you've been through it and you know exactly what you want now
Okay, that was pile three whoever had pile three Chanel pile two whoever has pile two
Starts out with
The cold shoulder maybe somebody's you're giving somebody the cold shoulder or somebody's giving you the cold shoulder
But you know and also but it's also you know, he's a blanket on his he's a blanket there
So it's like maybe you can warm it up a little bit, right or keep it like so it's not too cold
What else we got? Oh, we have the devil and as a goat. Okay, number two
Yeah, I think go greatest all time the yeah, you like that Queen of Swords card. Yeah
Um, this this the go-kart is actually the capricorn card. So, you know
Alexander and I are both January 7th. And so we're both we're both the goat, right?
But I love this go-kart and this goat actually has a little bit like fires is like moving and kind of moving fast
I'm doing something right. Okay. Oh
We also have four of pentacles. This is almost like
It's almost like a little group effort at something,
like working together or something,
but it's like everyone has their own cards
that they're kind of keeping close.
It looks like everyone might not be showing
all their cards in this situation.
Ooh, and we have the King of Cups.
Okay, the King of Cups is somebody that's,
you know, usually masculine energies
that's become very emotionally balanced
because you've been through a lot of emotions.
And so also I think the King of Cups likes to have a drink too.
But
Kim pulls his liquor. You know, he's probably the kind of guy that can have a couple drinks and still drive and
Still safe in the car. Okay. Now whoever had the pile one. Here's the final pile
What do we got?
We have
Uh, the fiddle leaf big. Okay
There's a plant. Okay, and it's a big plant. Okay, and the fiddle leaf. Okay, because it has these interesting
It's just it looks like a person almost or like a bird or something like that, but it's it's a it's a plant
Okay, so maybe something's not what it seems. Okay
We have oh the tower. Okay. I just had a tower recently
Unfortunately, but you know what a tower see it kind of like can burn down the forest or and then it's like you're like
Oh, no, it's destroyed or it's like oh look at all this clear space
And now they now the soil is good to grow some stuff or something because it's like, you know been
You know burn. Oh and look at we have okay. We have the nine of swords. Oh, you're not alone. What does that say?
Oh, we have a can't no
Well, we have the King of Swords because so we had the Queen of Swords now we have the King of Swords
the King of Swords is a very similar energy to the Queen of Swords, but I would say it's kind of like a Gemini Aquarius
Probably energy that
Is really good communicator
But also it's like in hurt feelings because they have that sword and the sword can cut
You know and feeling like it's just like you know words can hurt feelings sometimes, but it there's feelings, right?
We got the chariot again, and so this pile whoever it is this pile is also gonna be moving forward
Especially from this tower. It looks like it's like you're just speeding away from it and maybe
Maybe you know you are made Gemini. Ah
Yeah, when it came well, is it true of Mercury's having people come back from your past and resolving things?
Yeah, I'll tell you about the Mercury retrograde we're in right now because I do believe we're in a pretty
We're pretty
strong mercury retrograde right now.
So let me see, I'll read about it in the science.
Mercury retrograde.
Mercury retrograde, of course,
mercury is the fastest moving planet closest to the sun.
And so it has to do with like communication
and air science.
So it says the dates are, okay.
So mercury is going to retrograde
its spells big change, okay?
Here's what it means for each zodiac sign.
The retrograde ends on November 29th, okay?
So it's all this month,
it's gonna be weird communication, right?
Through the shadow period continues until,
oh, though the shadow period continues until mid-December
as Mercury retraces its steps,
use this entire period wisely.
You'll enter a 2026 with greater clarity,
better communication,
and a stronger sense of what truly deserves your attention.
Okay.
It says, the retrograde occurs primarily in Sagittarius before dipping back into Scorpio,
blending philosophical truth seeking with emotional depth.
Which is a Scorpio and the philosophical truth-seeking is of course decided tears the centaur
It's a period for human for internal processing rather than external progress a time where a universe
Crackily insists we review before we move forward
With half of our cosmic players already retrograde this month including Jupiter Saturn Neptune in Uranus the energies decidedly introspective
Here's how murky retrograde in November will affect each sign. Okay, so let's see. So if you are in Aries
It says, higher learning, adventure, philosophical conversations take center stage during the
retrograde.
You may find yourself revisiting travel plans, educational pursuits, or even spiritual beliefs
you've thought you've moved past.
An old teacher or mentor or friend from abroad
can resurface valuable insights.
While Mars and the Sagittarius keeps you
feeling bold and restless,
Mercury Retrograde asks you to slow your roll slightly.
The course you've been considering,
wait until late November to commit.
The person you've been debating ideology with,
there's more to understand before you take a firm stance.
Use the time to try to think deeply
about what freedom truly means to you.
Okay, for Taurus, it revolves around the intimacy zone,
the shared resources, and transformation.
So financial matters involving others,
joining accounts, investments, inheritance issues,
or even your partner's income.
could require a renegotiation.
You might also find yourself processing past trauma,
work with a therapist if you need to.
Gemini, your ruler Mercury goes retrograde
in your relationship sector,
making this a particularly significant period
for you, Gemini.
Between November 9th and 13th especially,
expect miscommunication with partners,
romantic or business to be intensified,
and X could reach out,
or you might suddenly see a sudden current relationship
from an entirely different perspective.
This is an ideal timing to reassess what you need from the closest commitments, though
not the time to make dramatic decisions.
Contracts and agreements should be postponed, if possible.
If you've been contemplating a couple's therapy or serious conversation with a business partner,
use the period for internal clarity first.
Remember the truth is still revealing itself.
For cancers, your daily rhythms, health practices, and work routines come under Mercury's reflective
influence this month.
serves you or noticing patterns in your wellness approach to the adjustment.
An old health issue could flare up asking for attention and avoiding.
Considered a cosmic health audit for Leo romance creativity pleasure projects
following Mercury's backward gaze this month.
You might reconnect with an old flame not necessarily to rekindle but to gain
perspective on what connection taught you.
Okay, your heart knows more than your head right now.
Pervergos, it's home, family and emotional foundations
are highlighted.
You might have important conversations with family members
that require revisiting old dynamics
or unresolved issues and housing matters, okay?
For Libras,
Communication sector lights up during Mercury-Richard grade.
You might hear back from someone from the past,
perhaps an old schoolmate or local connection.
This is an excellent timing to return to writing projects,
redo coursework,
and finally have that conversation you've been avoiding
to ensure exceptionally clear and all communications
where you assume others understand,
may need an explicit stating.
Um, Scorpio, it's about money matters as it goes through the financial sector before
depicting the Scorpio review the budget, uh, you know, let lost items could reappear.
You might reconnect with with forgotten resources, whether money, skills or possessions for
It begins in Sagittarius, making this an intense personal period of reflection.
You may feel more introspective than usual, miscommunications about you or involving you
are likely.
People may misunderstand your intentions or words, avoid major personal decisions or
dramatic changes to your appearance.
Capricorn, your subconscious dreams and spiritual life receive Mercury's attention during the
You might experience vivid dreams that offer insights about unresolved issues,
or find yourself drawn to therapy, meditation, or reflective practices.
Old psychological patterns may surface, asking for conscious acknowledgment.
Not a time for pushing forward in the external world, instead,
honoring your need to retreat and internal processing.
Past secrets could emerge.
You might suddenly understand something about your history that was previously unclear.
Rest and trust, this inward journey is preparing you
for the ambitious year ahead. Sometimes withdrawal is the most positive action.
For Aquarius' friendship, community connections, and social circles come under review,
you might hear from that old friend assess current friendships and notice group dynamics that need
Technology related to social media can prove glitchy, and plans to friends can require rescheduling.
A social group or organization you are once involved with might resurface with opportunities or simply foreclosure.
For now, quality or quantity in your social world should be best.
And finally, Pisces.
Career, public reputation, and professional goals are highlighted during...
this mercury retrograde work projects may face delays or require revision. This is not ideal
timing for job interviews, launching business or negotiating career moves, though if they're
unfavorable, triple check all the details. Use November to audit your professional direction.
Are you on the path that genuinely fulfills you? What adjustments might serve your highest calling?
You have the clarity to move forward purposely. Okay. Well, isn't that great? Now, let me see.
No, they can I bought female and male Gemini are different personality too. Yeah, I would say they are
The person between May and June Gemini's aren't the same. Yeah, my dad was a June Gemini like and you know, because
June Gemini's are like Trump is a June Gemini
They're very
Like it goes towards the faster like more of the mercury in it
I think and then it's like I think it's a little slowed down in May. It's like because it has the tourists next like so close to it
Virgo is your older brother and a twin person with your twin brother. Oh, wow
Um
And that's why it feels like home. Jamie. Yeah, you're you're gem and I
What's the opinion about May Gemini person like you?
Okay, well, okay.
So, you know, May is usually a tourist month.
And so it's kind of between tourists.
And so is there a little bit,
probably more stubborn and not as like fast moving
because Gemini is a really fast thinking sign, everything.
It's still fast.
They still think fast, but it's the more
has a earth grounding in earth.
I think that the ones in
June are more next to cancer. And so it's closer to the emotional, you know, watery side on the
June side, right? So my dad was a Gemini in June. My mom was a cancer in July. And
there are signs right next to each other. It can be really, really different.
But I think they you know, I think that's a good combination. It's like I just
So I just familiar with the June Gemini and also Trump is a few days from my dad
Gemini rules like communication. It's mercury, right? So fast-moving
Really really good communicators and especially those June
Does June Gemini's those are chatter bugs those are chatter boxes, right?
Like to chat communicate good you're communicating good you're stubborn a little bit. Yeah, you got you probably got a little closer to torus
You know, which is like, um, let's see
Taurus is
It's a good question. I'm starting to think. Um, earth
You're also a little bit talkative, but you have a good sense. Okay, like towards oh towards the rule by Venus
Yeah, it's real by Venus. And so tourists are like more into like
The luxury and like they're not as hard workers as the June people but the June people the June ones are
Really, they don't mean you hardly need to work because it's like stuff just is coming and stuff like that
It's always come. It's like money comes out of thin air. It's it's also rules of fiat currency
you're a bit talkative, but you have good sense.
Well, that's good.
Yeah.
I think Gemini are usually gonna be very good talkers.
It's just like that mercury is that the tongue,
the gift of gab and a kind of loyal, yeah.
Yeah, Gemini's also can be like the evil twin
I kind of think of it as like Pisces is like, you know polarities like a
Fish in opposite directions, but the Gemini are basically like two twins, but they're both evil
I don't know if that makes sense, you know. Yeah, but not but not in a bad way, right?
I think in a good way and so
Um, but oh my gosh, tourists can be such a pain in the butt sometimes because it's like you're like come on like
And they're like very slow
They just want to sit under the tree and like, you know sitting this shade and like you do nice like little picnic
And you're like, come on. Let's go. We got to go. We got to go and it's like they're just like
It's like sitting. Oh, I love that. You know, I love like, you know, beautiful
things and
Uh, they're very very
Very you're not evil because you're stubborn one. Yeah, you're not the bad evil one
Yeah, I don't really think they're bad, but it's like it's kind of like not bad. They're not evil
But it's like they're mainly like they're both
They egg each other on rather than their opposites
So maybe it's whether good or evil. They're gonna be very similar. Okay, I
Can
Let's see how about I can do I can do some prophecies, and then I'll probably go get a McRib and a copy or something like that
I mean open my period
Or if you want you guys want to actually we I can show you my
My website and then we can like take the quiz if you want because there's a quiz on it and I'll show you so cold
I'm really annoyed that I can't
fix the
The mailing list integration is not working for some reason, but here we go. Okay, so this is really cool
If you want to see this cold sticky website, I'll see some of the features of it
And I'm gonna do a longer presentation about it, but it is looking really cool
Do I have a new AI song today? I do you probably I do I was but I'm having trouble with the generation and then I like
So I will show you something. I'll show you I will play something a little bit. So here is the
Cult of Psyche. So this is the website. Okay, so I go to the dashboard
Okay, I can go to Cult of Psyche. Okay, so this is the premier occult open panel in Tarot Sanctuary
If you want to watch the live stream you click on watch the live stream and look I'm on I'm on kick
And it puts it on the website so if I'm not ever not around or you don't know where I am
You can always go here, and I will have a schedule usually I'll try to make a schedule and have it more organized
Has some stream etiquette look
Encourage fish taco references discourage, you know anything that kills the vibe
Okay, there is a quiz. Oh, yeah, there's also a token system. This is really cool. So if you go tokens
You can like, I think, you can sign in, right?
Okay, so that's not set up yet, but it will be, okay.
It was working, but okay.
I'm still right in the middle, but let's see the quiz.
Okay, I know that works for sure.
Okay, it's working, yeah, okay.
So this is the level of devotion quiz, okay?
Discover your spiritual archetype within the cold of psyche.
Answer nine questions to rebuild your path.
Okay, let me see if I can.
Okay, you can say I'm an IT engineer. Oh, you like that you like the website. Yeah, I think it looks pretty good
I think it looks pretty good. I'm trying my best. I also has like, you know, a member
Okay, yes, I need to repair it as soon as possible. I'm working with a really cool program, but it does
Like allow you to just do a little bit of time. I put the
The program in the in the chat earlier me. I'll get it back again
You can sign up for this.
It's actually, I think it's based in Asia somewhere,
this company, but it's really, really awesome software
that you can basically tell what you want
and it will basically create it
without you needing to know specific coding.
I'm not very good at coding, right?
So...
If I go share with a friend I can copy and you can check it out
And if you check it out, I think it's free and if you sign up even for free. I will get
Credits and then I'll be able to work on my site more because I need I need to I need more credits
And so I'd really appreciate if you check out this website. There's the invitation right there
Yeah, and you and you can be like almost like an IT engineer too because you don't really you don't need to know
How to code you just have to know like what you want and it's like it's been a learning process
I've had to start from scratch a couple times, but they've been really good at
Refunding or like giving you credits if you like, you know, don't use the credits, right?
You can say hey didn't work out sending your link. You send the link of what the conversation was with the
Program and then they'll usually send me a lot of credits back. So they've been really generous with that I would say
It's very very cool though. It's a very cool very cool website and I'm kind of a little bit addicted because it's basically
I'm building the side of my dreams, right?
But it's got a little bit to go right so we're still working on it
Okay, let me see
You say I say that CZ. Oh, yeah, you said I know how to build a website in technology
Yeah, cuz I've been on enough websites to like know what I want and I wanted to do that
Think the psyche verse like to kind of like a IR, you know IP to kind of similar directory
then it's like turned into the turn to the cult with the memberships instituted into it and then
It's gonna have like daily tokens and then you can use the tokens to like
do these
Learn these rich learn the rituals. There's stuff revealed along the way. There's a whole cult lore. There's whole stuff to reveal
There's different levels of it
It's like I'm pretty cool. And so let me see if I can go to my
music generator
You met some people on YouTube
From America with bad skills with the technology. Yeah, you know, you know, well, I think thing that is is pretty good
I think he but he's Canadian, right? He's he's a coder. I just I can't do coding. It's just I don't have the patience
I can't even like believe
How it's figuring out I was like, how's it so smart? Okay
Let me see.
OK, let me see if I can generate something real quick.
I'll try this one more time.
I'm having a lot of trouble generating stuff today.
And then I'll go probably get a frigana something
No, Sean make rib. I'm thinking right
That there we go, let's see if that works today
Who he didn't know how to use in the stream yard link using it YouTube. Oh
Lord Vader. Yeah, we get Lord Vader's today. I did a I did a strip tease there. It's pretty it's pretty fun
What do I have I have the I have a few songs. Let me see
I think it's okay.
This silence stitched my ribs with smoke
Build altars out of every word I never spoke
My mercy was the one that never...
Against the council of my bones watch you slip into the black
I did just make another one, but it didn't do the whole thing.
So this is like an Indian. I posted a lot about her lately, and she's a green Indian goddess.
She's an avatar of Kali. Her name is Matangi, and she represents...
You know, if you've heard of Sarah Swatsey, she's like the tantric version of Sarah Swatsey where she represents kind of like the outcast
she takes
offerings of leftover food and like even spoiled food and you know, she likes kind of like pollution and smoke and stuff
But
And there's a lot of interesting things if you meditate on so this is an actual
This is by someone named Kali Dasa and it's translated. I do recommend listening to the Sanskrit
but
introducing to a Western audience who's not really familiar with
Sanskrit and that I think it's a good interesting way to introduce the goddess and so let's see how you'd like this
Let's see if it worked. I haven't seen it yet. So let's see if it worked out good. Okay. I have a look
Okay
I meditate on the daughter of Matanga
Who plays the Veena made of precious gems
Lazy with divine exuberance, blessed with sweet words and shining like a blue gem.
My salutations to the mother of the universe.
She of forehands, she who wears the crescent moon.
Whose form is saffron, who holds flower, sugarcane, rope, arrow.
The gold and the sacred pundarica.
Bless me with a sight long glance, O daughter of sage Matanga,
My emerald green mother who lives in the Kadamba forest,
And blesses with all that is good.
Victory to the daughter of Matanga, To she who resembles the nilot pala flower,
Who delights in music and the playful parrot.
Victory to the mother who dwells in Kadamba and Vilwa forests,
On the gem island in the sea of nectar.
Beloved of the worlds
She whose hair dances with music whose curls shine with crescent light whose eyelashes are the arrows of love whose words cool the universe like nectar
Whose musk till a cup rings joy who is Lexmi whose voice is a vena blending with bees drawn to the musk upon her neck
She shines with divine ornaments, recognized by sages wearing palm-leaf ear ornaments
And nilat pala studs brighter than moonlight, she grants wealth, happiness, and all wishes
She smiles with arc, a camphor, and tembula, holds the lotus and the fina, her lips red as bimba fruit, her conch like neck born of the cosmic ocean.
She is the embodiment of art, voluptuous radiant with gem garlands, the personification of all that is good.
Her arms shine like young tendrils with gemmed armlets
Her bangles radiance circling the world
Her hands rival lotus blooms
Her fingers shine like the moon with jeweled rings
Worshiped by Indra and all devas
Surrounded by the eternal light
She is a three-world beauty humble in her golden grace
With hair dark as water plants encircling her deep navel
Her speech is alluring her golden belt defeats commas bow her silk studded with gems and diamond bells rival mirrors valleys
Her thighs glow red as Palasha blossoms her grace flows without end
She is dark beauty the lion gated goddess whose crescent like
Okay, yeah, and it ends kind of abruptly because it's in it the whole thing, but I think it's a good start
I like to
Okay, I'm gonna go see if I can get a McRib
I will maybe post some shorts in the meantime because I have some published from the last few shows
So why don't you check out the shorts for a little bit? I'll be back later tonight. We're gonna have a fun night
Okay, it's Saturday night
Everyone get out get out your party clothes. Okay. I love you. I'll be back soon